Lakshmikant Tyagi

PERSONAL DATA

PLACE AND DATE OF BIRTH: Agra, India | 01 May 1998

ADDRESS: 5-C 44/18 Shambhunagar, 282010, Agra, India

PHONE: 7051916870

EMAIL: lktyagi76@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I'm a Full stack Web Developer and Application Developer with more than 3 years of professional experience. In my works I always try to combine aesthetic with functional aspects, looking for the right balance to communicate without annoying. What makes a great website? Here's my opinion: a successful website should be attractive but easy to read. A fascinating message, together with an immediate understanding. Original content and easily traceable information: that's my recipe. I have always been studying new techniques to improve my knowledge, face new challenges and do best in my Creation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DEC 2018 -MAY 2019

Full stack Developer at ByodBuzz Andhra Pradesh,India

worked as a Full stack Developer Intern at Byodbuzz startup. Developed a Web app using Django and worked with Javascript Frameworks like Angular Node and React and Managing both UI/frontend and backend of the application. Also worked with web scraping and web automation.

MAY -JULY 2018

Full stack Developer at AS TAXSOFT Agra, India

worked as a Full stack Developer Intern at Vizack startup . Developed Web-apps using Javascript Frameworks like Angular Node and React and Managing both UI/frontend and backend of the application.

MAR-APR 2018

MEAN stack Developer at Vizack Bengaluru, India

worked as a MEAN stack Developer Intern at Vizack startup. Developed a Web app using Javascript Frameworks like Node and React and Managing both UI/frontend and backend of the application.

DEC 2017-FEB 2018

JAVA Spring Developer at PRINCSYS INCORPORATION, India

Developed a web application using JAVA MVC Framework like Spring to connect whole campus from student to Chancellor and Developed a Database using PostgreSQL.

DEC 2016-APR 2017

Full stack web Developer Intern at QWIKSOCIAL

Developed Many website for the clients of qwiksocial using Javascript ,Wordpress CMS and E-commerce platform using Magento .Also,worked as Business Development Executive intern in same Organization.

EDUCATION

2015- 2019 Bachelor Of Technology in COMPUTER SCIENCE, SMVDU, Jammu, India

GPA: 6.5/10

2014 XII Examination SYMBOYZIA SECONDARY SCHOOL

PERCENTAGE: 81.6

2012 CBSE X Examination Symboyzia Secondary School

GPA:9.4/10

CERTIFICATES

SEP 2017 Completed the Internet Of Things workshop Conducted by Intel Corporation.

SEP 2015 Secured 2 Position in WebMaster Competition in University.

LANGUAGES

HINDI: Mothertongue

ENGLISH: Fluent

COMPUTER SKILLS

Frontend: HTML5 CSS3 BootStrap Javascript Angular ReactJS Wordpress

Backend: PHP AJAX XML Node.js SQL DBMS MySQL MongoDB

Programming: Python JAVA C++

Software: Adobe Experience Manager Photoshop Dreamweaver

Other: Django Machine Learning

INTERESTS AND ACTIVITIES

Technology, Open-Source, Programming Paradoxes in Decision Making, Marketing , Behavioural Finance Cricket, Table-Tennis, Travelling